WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Previously on
"The Vampire Diaries"...
You have the ability
to keep living
inside someone
else's body.
Katherine Pierce
has permanent control
of Elena Gilbert's body.
I want my daughter,
I want immortality,
and I want
Stefan Salvatore.
I know how bad
I screwed up.
I need you.
We're over.
Why would Nadia
be compelling me?
I need a crash course
on all things Elena Gilbert,
and I figured who
knows her better
than her compellable
best friend?
So tell me, now that
you've slept with Klaus,
how was it?
Oh, my God.
And you are?
My backup.
Wes has
this sick little scheme
to destroy vampires
by making them feed
on each other.
I can see how this
might be a problem.
You think the fella
loved milking cows?
Probably. Then she
became one,
so he drank himself
into oblivion,
she cheated
with the pastor.
Hey. Just because
you lost your true love
doesn't mean you have to
dump on others.
There's no love in there.
Look at that picture.
It's old,
and the milkmaid's
nowhere to be found.
It's just pathetic
old farmer John.
Manners. It's impolite
to speak ill of our hosts.
Doubt he'll mind.
Somebody's cranky.
It's been almost 8 hours
since you last fed,
so I suppose
that's about right.
You're timing me?
You feed on vampires now.
I am a vampire.
The only way to
assure my safety
is to know how long
you can last
before your next fix.
Or you can just
leave.
I don't abandon
my friends, Damon.
Besides, if you hadn't
come with me to kill Dr. Wes,
he wouldn't have stuck
you with that nasty virus.
Ah! Just in time.
Hello!
What did you do?
What's happening?
Uh, you died,
but luckily, you had
my blood in your system,
so when you drink this,
you'll feel much better.
There you are.
Good boy.
What was that?
That was blood.
You're a vampire.
Congratulations.
I'm a what?
I know.
It's overwhelming,
and Damon will explain
more in a bit,
but before he does,
settle a bet.
Your wife.
Where is she?
Wait. I drink blood now?
Again, we'll explain
everything.
Where's your wife?
She's gone.
She left me years ago.
Pastor?
Pharmacist.
Yes. I will take
that as a win for me,
not for you.
Oh, stop trying
to scare me, Damon.
I'm not leaving you.
I'm the only friend you have left.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.MY-SUBS.com/
Roman empire.
476 A.D. sacked
by the goths.
Han dynasty.
220 A.D.
Holy Roman empire.
Not really an empire,
but 1648.
There goes
your perfect score.
What? No.
That was right.
No, no, no.
The book says 1806.
Heh. Ok. Well, 1806 may
technically be right,
but it was
the peace of Westphalia
that truly ended
the empire,
and that was in 1648.
Trust me.
I may have done
a paper
on the holy Roman
empire in High School.
Well, if you want to
pass the test,
I suggest you write down
exactly what's
in your textbook.
Oh. Caroline's here.
I asked the sheriff to
help me track down Damon.
You were right.
He's off the rails.
This is from my mom.
Let me guess...
Missing persons and animal attacks.
Check and check.
There's
something else.
All the victims were
found inside their homes
without their head,
and there skin
was desiccated.
Damon's feeding
on vampires.
I shouldn't have
let him go.
No! Uh-uh. No!
You are not turning
Damon's roosting chickens
into a Stefan Salvatore
guilt trip.
No one could have stopped him from
going after Wes the other night.
Guess Wes must have
injected him
with whatever he was
gonna give Elena
that makes vampires
feed on vampires.
Good news, bad news.
Bad news is that
when this happened to Jesse
we had to kill him,
but the good news is...
I'm sorry. Usually
there's some good news.
I have to find him.
Well, I can come
with you.
Elena, hey!
I didn't know
that you were here.
Well, Stefan has been
helping me study.
Oh. Stefan who doesn't
go to college.
Stefan who's
an expert in history.
Uh-huh. Um...
It's Tyler.
I haven't really
spoken to him
since, the, um,
incident.
The incident?
You mean the time
where he
almost killed you?
Hey.
Hey, have you
talked to Matt?
No. Why?
Because it turns out
Nadia's been compelling
him to forget things.
Matt said he was
gonna avoid her,
but now I haven't
heard from him.
Do you think that
he's in trouble?
He hasn't been home
or at work,
and his cell phone goes
straight to voicemail.
Ok. Well, I'll come
right over and...
No. That's not
why I called.
No. I know,
but I think that
we can figure
this out together.
I'll see you soon.
Maybe I should
come with you.
No. No. You deal
with Damon.
We can handle this.
Besides, it's time that
we move into the next phase
of our post-breakup,
pre-friendship
relationship timeline.
Ok. I'm gonna stay
out that one.
I'm gonna get
some clothes,
and you'll pick me up
at my dorm?
Sure.
Bad news is
Tyler hates you,
but the good news
is... hmm.
It'll be fine.
We both have weird
ex... friend situations.
We? There's nothing
weird going on
between Elena
and me.
Come on, Stefan!
First she tells you
that she's gonna fight
to get Damon back,
and then she rebreaks up
with him,
and now she's here
with you, her ex, studying?
She's here with
her friend studying
without the implied
quotes.
Look. I'm just saying that
Elena and Damon's breakup
is messy,
and you are not messy.
You're stable
and sane and...
And I'm about to spend 12
hours in a car with her alone,
so whatever
she's feeling
I'm sure I'll be able
to figure it out.
What's going on
with Matt?
Nothing.
Really? Because
Goldilocks
and the big bad wolf
are meeting to powwow
about him as we speak.
Fine. Matt found out
about you.
He what?!
Tyler gave him
vervain.
Kill him.
Katherine!
Kill him now.
He doesn't need
to die.
The vervain will be
out of his system soon,
and I've kept him out
of sight for two days,
so he hasn't
told anyone.
So you two have just been
tucked away, canoodling?
I don't even know
what that means.
We all love Matt Donovan.
Otherwise, he would have
been dead a long time ago,
but when it comes to keeping
my new doppelganger body
a secret,
nobody is that important.
I am going out of town
with Stefan
because he wants to
find Damon.
I thought you wanted
Damon out of the picture.
Meh. I do,
but I saw an opportunity
to be alone with Stefan
for a few days,
and, well, I took it.
And what happens when
you get too close,
too comfortable?
What happens
when you slip up?
Will you kill
your precious Stefan, too?
Using my own words
against me.
Now that's
a Petrova specialty.
Take care
of the Matt issue
before I get back
into town,
or I'll have to
do it myself.
It'll be fine.
I just need to convince
my friends that I'm ok.
I'll keep your secret.
No one has to die.
Relax.
Heh heh heh.
I'm not going to
syrup you to death.
What's canoodling?
I didn't realize you
liked to play with dolls.
Well, my brother likes
to make a big show,
set them up,
put their heads back on,
pretend like
it didn't happen.
I, on the other hand,
don't give a crap.
Well, we've got 8 hours
till you need to feed again.
I wonder,
what's New York like these days.
Crowded.
Perfect. Let's go.
Oh, what is that?
It's the obnoxious theme
song of the travelers.
Unh!
Aww.
As a man of science,
I always considered
magic a cheat.
Turns out I cheat.
How's the appetite?
Funny you should ask.
I was just craving a blond.
You're my patient zero,
Damon.
Couldn't let you ride
off into the sunseting a blond.
Without running
a few tests.
A few tests.
Well, one test.
Now that you're trapped
with only one source of food,
how long can you go before
you feed on your best friend?
You ever think
about getting a new car?
What are you
talking about?
This car's
a classic.
Yeah, and so is,
uh, Wright brothers' plane,
but you don't see people still
flying around in that thing.
You know, uh...
I appreciate you
being here,
but you didn't
have to come.
I told you
I'm doing this for you
because you're still
holding on to the hope
that maybe this is the time
that Damon can be saved.
And you don't think
he can?
Look. I know that he crossed
a line with Jeremy,
but, you know,
he's crossed many lines before.
You mean, when he
actually killed Jeremy?
Yes, I recall.
I'm just saying
you've never really
closed him off
like this before.
I mean, obviously,
I still care about Damon.
I guess I got my hopes up
too many times.
I want off the emotional
roller coaster
that is Damon's redemption.
You know, it's just...
It's dizzying.
Are you hungry?
Because I'm starving.
Um, sure.
What do you want?
Whatever you're having
but with a lot more salt
and maybe covered
in chocolate.
Coming right up.
Give it up, mate.
Those travelers sealed
this whole place up tight.
The spell can't
last forever.
Doesn't need to.
Wes only needs it
to last 8 hours,
remember?
Then he can come
back inside
and autopsy
my mangled corpse.
You're pretty zen
about all this.
Did you forget everything
I taught you in that cell?
Calmer heads
will always prevail.
Always the solider.
But you do have people
we can call,
like your brother
or your ex,
who can in turn find Wes
and threaten him
or maim him
or anything that doesn't
involve your fangs
on my neck.
My brother told me
to leave and not come back.
I'm not calling him.
So my life is not
worth your pride?
They won't come.
Or they will.
Then you might
hurt them.
Don't want to
risk, do you?
Me on the other hand...
I'm not gonna
feed on you.
I'll find another way.
Thank you.
Mmm. That's
good coffee.
Although I usually
take mine
with a little more
awkward silence.
Nice try,
but you don't take
anything with silence.
So Matt.
He's missing?
I don't know
if he's missing.
He just hasn't
been home in two days,
and he's not
answering his phone.
Matt?
Caroline!
What are you doing here?
Kind of wondering
the same thing.
Where the hell
have you been?
Did I give you
my sunglasses?
Oh. Hello.
I thought you said
they wouldn't be home.
Ok.
Rewind. Start over.
This whole time you've
been with Nadia?
It's a long story.
Nadia, come on in.
Hmm.
Oh, man.
Hey. Can you hold this
for a second?
Yeah.
Careful. It has
grease on it.
Oh, ok.
I have no idea how
this hose ripped out,
but we're not gonna
be able to go anywhere
until I get a new one.
I guess I'll see if
that mechanic has a spare.
You weren't careful
at all?
What? What?
Ohh! I love this shirt.
You loved that shirt.
Great. Awesome
that's just awesome.
Now there's grease
all over your face.
Ugh!
Well, you've got all that
engine stuff on you,
and I clearly
have to change.
I saw a hotel, like,
a couple streets down that way.
Do you think
we should get a room
so that we can shower while
we're waiting for the car?
No. I should probably stay
here in case they finish early,
but you can go.
Give them
your phone number.
I assume that your phone
does receive
incoming calls, right?
Or is it
from the Han dynasty
just like your car?
That's funny.
Will you grab my bag?
Sure.
Be right there.
I was on my way
out of town,
and then there
she was,
sitting
on the front steps,
waiting for me.
Subtlety's not
my strong suit.
I felt bad
about compelling him
and bad about snapping
your neck.
Again, subtlety.
So why haven't you
been answering your phone?
Uh, I lost it
the first night.
- First night where?
- Atlantic city.
I'd never been,
neither had Matt.
1 drink led to 3
and to 5
and then, uh...
The rest is
kind of a blur.
Yeah, because she's
compelling you!
Caroline, I'm
wearing vervain.
She's not
compelling me.
Where have you been
the last two days?
I told you. She's
not compelling me.
We're having fun.
Oh. Fun!
Just like the time
she buried you alive!
Whoo! Pop open
the champagne!
I thought you said she'd be
cool with us hanging out.
And what the hell is
that supposed to mean?
Uh...
It means you've done
nothing but judge Matt
since he walked
through that door
when everyone here knows
you're not exactly
winning friends
with your romantic choices.
Isn't that right, Tyler?
I don't want to
be a part of this.
She's just trying to get
under our skin to distract us.
From what?
This is Matt we're
talking about.
Did you forget that time
he went to Europe with Rebekah
after she ran
his truck off the road?
You're not seriously
buying all this?
Hell of a lot easier
to buy
than other things
that have happened.
So what did you do,
bring your entire closet?
Well, I didn't know
how long we'd be gone,
and let's be honest.
Damon's spirals require
a little more
than an overnight bag.
Mm-hmm.
We'll get him back.
He's, uh... he's hurt,
but he's not a lost cause.
What makes you
think that?
Because I know what
he's going through.
What do you mean?
You don't know what it's
like being in love with you.
You know,
when you and I were together,
every single atom
in my body told me
that it was
the right thing,
that we were
the perfect fit,
and that kind
of love,
it can change
your whole life,
and then when somebody
who made you feel that way
suddenly stops,
the vacuum
is just...
I get it.
They built a whole
prophecy around it.
He's not handling
it right,
but he's not gone.
You need a refill.
I should go wash up.
Ok.
Towing chains.
Farmer's best friend.
In about an hour, mine.
Take a seat.
They're not gonna let us out
of here until I kill you...
Or you kill me.
Don't be dramatic.
We'll work
something out.
There's no cure,
Enzo, not for this.
You've given it all
of two days.
That's what you do,
isn't it?
There's a problem,
you run.
You did it to me,
you did it
to your girl.
Because when I stay,
I destroy things.
We're not all as fragile
as you think we are.
What the hell
are you doing?
Calling for backup.
I thought I told
you not call them.
And I told you your pride isn't
worth either of our lives.
Oh, my God. Damon?
Hello, Stefan.
How wonderful to hear
your beautiful
feminine voice.
Enzo. What the hell
do you want?
I'm in a spot
of trouble actually.
Where's Damon?
Oh, he's here,
salivating,
about to chomp
into my neck and feed
until my head pops off
in a grotesque
but slightly
comical fashion.
Wes infected him?
You know about the virus.
Good. We could use a hand.
Wes enlisted some
of those singing witches
and trapped us
in the house.
Do not come here!
He doesn't want to
risk feeding on you.
That's sweet really,
but you'll be fine.
Besides if he does
feed on you,
I have orders
to kill him.
Ok. Um,
text me the address to my phone,
and we'll be there
as soon as we can.
Fine. And, uh, ticktock.
I managed
to restrain him,
but you know how persistent
Damon can be
when he wants something.
We'll be there soon.
You say something?
No. Heh.
It'll be all right, mate.
They'll come,
and we'll sort something out.
Or they'll come,
and I'll feed on them.
Those are also options.
As long as I live,
I'm good.
Joking. Kind of.
If you were aiming for my heart,
you missed.
Don't worry.
I wasn't.
Chains were a good idea.
Now I can see exactly
how strong he becomes
when enraged.
Conclusion... very strong.
Boy, do I miss
that indestructible Augustine cage
right about now.
Damon, stop! Damon, stop!
Stop! Please, Damon, stop!
Damon, stop!
Stop, please!
Damon! Aah! Aah!
What did you do
to him?
My friends here raised
the acidity of your blood.
There must be some
witchy explanation for it,
but Damon's basically
drinking hydrochloric acid.
I suggest you leave
before the spell wears off.
And go where...
With you?
There's one more thing
I need from you.
Then I'll let you go
for good.
The other option is
to stay in here
with your cannibal friend
and see how long you last.
Go, Enzo!
I tried to kill you.
I'll do it again.
Go, Enzo!
Car's done.
I'll be right there.
Hey, um...
Would mind grabbing
me my shirt?
It's the... the green
one right on top.
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
This is...
This is wrong.
We, uh...
You and Damon
just split up.
You don't have to,
um... you're right.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I was just in the moment.
I shouldn't have.
Yeah.
We have a long night
ahead of us,
so maybe we should...
Yeah. Um, you know what?
Why don't you go, um,
settle up the bill,
and I'll... I'll
finish packing?
Heh.
Who do you think
Stefan loves more,
Damon or Elena?
Why are you
calling me?
Damon has been infected
by the ripper virus,
and I know exactly
where he is,
so if I can get Damon
to attack me,
the only way to save me would
be for Stefan to kill him.
You're going to make
Stefan kill his brother?
Dark, even for you.
Thank you.
So how goes it
with Matty blue eyes?
Dead yet?
Still working on it.
Good luck with your plan
to win Stefan's love.
So... I'm curious.
We spent a few days
together now.
Canoodling?
Canoodling. Exactly.
It seems like you went
through all this trouble
to save your mom, but she only
seems interested in Stefan.
That's Katherine.
I didn't expect
mother-daughter boozy brunches.
Yeah, but you did
expect something.
Are you going to play
a card or what?
Look. I've been
where you are.
My mom used to disappear
for weeks at a time
and then show up one
day out of the blue
like nothing
happened.
Before you knew it,
I'd be at the stove,
making her
a grilled cheese.
This isn't like that.
Isn't it?
She decides when you're worth it
on her watch,
but guess what.
You're never gonna
be as interesting
as the next guy she
wants to sleep with.
Matt, you'd say
anything to help Elena.
I'm not an idiot.
You are if you think
that Katherine's
gonna choose you...
Because she's not.
Do you know why you found yourself
making all those sandwiches?
Because the second your mom
walked back into your life,
you forgot all those
horrible things that she did
because at the end
of the day,
she's still your mom,
2and you love her.
Give me your wrist.
The vervain is gone.
Our fun is over.
Wait.
Since I'm gonna
forget this anyway...
What was that for?
Thank you.
If I'm gonna be threatened
and held against my will,
I could think
of worse scenarios.
What the hell?
What'd you expect?
Elena's my best friend.
I'll always protect her.
It just sucks.
You were the only decent
person in this town.
And I still am,
and so are you.
You could have killed me
this morning, and you didn't.
You're not like her,
and you know it.
Forget everything you're
not supposed to know.
We partied,
we slept together,
then I left.
Good-bye.
Going somewhere?
Actually, I am,
and you're in my way.
Matt, are you ok?
Yeah. Why?
What's going on in here?
You texted me
from Nadia's phone.
So you compelled
him again.
And they say blonds
are dumb.
What are you doing to him? Tell me!
Nadia, stop!
You may not
remember, Matt,
but this is
your fault.
Trust me.
Young hybrid beats
old vampire every time!
Wait a second!
Does anyone want to tell me
how this is
my fault?
Elena.
Don't.
Do not.
I said don't!
You come in here,
you ain't coming out.
What exactly
happened here?
I wanted revenge,
got stuck with
the vampire virus,
almost killed
my last friend.
Typical Damon.
Enzo texted me
the address here.
Damon, we're here
to help you.
You can't help me.
I feed on
vampires now.
You're
both vampires.
Do yourselves
a favor and leave.
Well, that's not
gonna happen.
Stay back!
I'm not afraid
of you, Damon.
Neither am I.
You better get out.
What the hell is
wrong with you?
I'm proving to you that you're
not a lost cause, Damon.
Elena.
See?
Ugh!
Damon, you can
resist this.
You can do it. Why?
Because you love me,
and that love is stronger
than any craving.
Get away from me,
Elena.
Elena, he's gonna
kill you.
No. No.
He's not going to.
You can do this, Damon.
Fight it.
There you go.
Turn around.
Aah!
Damon, stop!
Damon, let go of her,
let go of her!
Stefan!
Let go!
No! He's going...
To kill me!
Here, Damon.
Look over here.
You smell that?
Feed on me, not her.
That's good.
Feed on me.
Well, the only
thing Matt remembers
is that they
slept together.
Well...
So...
Care.
I never said sorry.
I was pissed,
but...
No excuses, ok?
Look. We can get
past this together.
Ok? I just want us to
be good again, you know?
I said I was sorry.
I didn't say
I was past it.
Of course.
Obviously.
I mean, Rome wasn't
built in a day.
How evolved do you
think I am?
You slept with Klaus.
You slept with the guy
that killed my mom.
What's a fair amount of time
for me to get past that?
A week, a month?
Tell me. What sounds
right to you?
Ok. You made
your point.
Look. I'm not
trying to be a dick,
but the idea
of us being good,
it's not gonna happen.
Understood.
Ugh.
I know you can't
help yourself,
but if you bring
home a rabid animal,
you're gonna
get bit.
Never should have
told you to leave.
Uh!
I'm gonna kill you,
Stefan.
Maybe not today,
maybe not tomorrow,
but at some point
I'm gonna rip open up your throat,
and you're
gonna die.
Oh, come on, Damon.
You think I'm afraid
of a ripper?
Who do you think
invented the word?
You know that feeling you get
when you're around vampire blood,
that burning
in your veins?
I feel that
on a daily basis,
and there's a way
to control it.
And let me guess...
It'd bring you
no greater pleasure
than to teach me.
No. It's a good guess,
but right now,
I'm gonna go get you
a little bit more vervain,
and them I'm gonna
have a drink,
and I'm gonna let you think about
what a royal pain in the ass
you've been lately.
You're my brother.
I'm not gonna
give up on you.
I never will.
She has.
You talking about Elena?
Mm-hmm.
She practically got
herself killed
to prove a point today.
You remember the vampire
ripper Jesse?
When he attacked me,
Elena had to kill him,
but if there was
the slightest chance
that there was
another way to stop him,
she would have taken it.
Yeah, so?
She knew it would be impossible
for me to resist her blood,
and then she just
kicked you a stake
and essentially told
you to kill me.
So what are you saying?
You saying that Elena
wanted me to kill you?
You got another
excuse, hmm?
That's what I thought.
Well...
I could use a steak.
You're chipper.
That must mean
Damon is dead.
Not quite.
In fact, he
continues to be
the bane
of my existence,
but...
Stefan and I
had a moment. Heh.
Don't worry.
I'll keep the details to myself,
but it definitely reaffirmed
his feelings for Elena,
I.E. me. Heh.
So, uh, it's only
a matter of time.
Sounds like you're going
to get everything you want.
Of course I will.
Assuming that you took
care of the Matt situation.
Your secret is safe.
Perfect. So I'm in
a really good mood right now,
which means I don't
really feel like worrying
whatever's making
you mopey.
You won't have to worry
about me for much longer.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Tyler Lockwood bit me.
Hey. When'd
you get here?
Eh, about 1 1/2
of these ago.
Hmm.
You were right.
I brought this
on myself.
I knew the Klaus thing was
gonna come with consequences.
Guess now I just
have to deal with it
and learn
from my mistakes.
Glad I could help.
So did you find Matt?
Yes, and Tyler
was right.
Nadia's been compelling
him to forget things.
What do you mean?
What kind of things?
Who knows? He tried
to message me,
but Nadia
stopped him.
"Help. K"
was all I got.
Huh.
So you and Elena?
What's the verdict?
Um, well, the verdict is
she's acting strange.
She kissed me.
Excuse me?
Yeah. My car broke down,
so we got a hotel room
so she could shower...
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
You guys got
a hotel room
with a shower?
Yeah, but it wasn't
like that.
I mean, I stopped
it obviously.
I couldn't do it
to Damon.
Yeah, but she could?
I just... I don't
get it.
She knows that this
would destroy him.
What is she doing?
That's what I mean.
It's like she's
given up on Damon,
and he thinks that
she was trying to get
me to kill him tonight.
No. I mean, she
may be mad at him,
but she would
never want him dead.
Unless...
Matt texted you,
"help. K,"
before Nadia
stopped him.
"K," as in Katherine,
and when Katherine
was dying,
Nadia figured out a way
to put Katherine's spirit
inside Nadia's body.
Yeah, but that
didn't happen
because Katherine
had a change of heart.
No. No. You don't
think that...
It's impossible that
she'd be...
We would have
noticed.
It's Elena.
We know her.
Oh, my God.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.MY-SUBS.com/