WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Previously on
"The Vampire Diaries"...
Wes had this scheme
to destroy vampires
by making them feed on each other.
- What's happening to you?
- Karma is happening to me.
My name is Nadia Petrova.
You are my mother.
This knife's the only thing
that will kill a passenger.
I passengered myself
into Elena's cute, little head.
She's acting strange.
She kissed me.
Matt texted "help K,"
as in "Katherine."
Oh, my God.
You won't have to worry
about me for much longer.
Tyler Lockwood bit me.
Good evening, sir.
If I could trouble
you for a moment.
I'm looking for someone.
Her name is Katerina Petrova.
She was last seen outside
of London in 1492.
She's on the run.
I need to find her.
I need to ask her
why she abandoned me.
Nadia?
Please.
I need to know.
Nadia, I'm right here.
I'm right here.
Uhh. I was dreaming how I searched
for you from village to village.
I know.
I heard you.
You said that I abandoned you.
You were ripped
from my arms as a baby.
It's completely different.
Not for a child without a mother.
You know, all this guilt is
really taking all the fun out of
this mother-daughter outing.
I'm sorry Tyler bit you, but
you're not going to die.
Did you ask Klaus for his blood?
Oh, my, you really are delirious.
Nadia, he would love nothing more
than to watch my daughter die.
And you don't want
to risk being outed.
No, I don't.
So, that's why I called him.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Dr. Maxfield.
And luckily for us, he'll love nothing
more than to study your blood.
Werewolf venom isn't
easy to come by.
Get away from me.
It's ok.
Nadia, it's ok.
Listen to your mother.
The venom in your blood is a toxin
with basic chemical properties.
Once I study its make-up, I can...
Create the antidote.
It's ok.
Come on, come on, honey.
There you go.
If I'd known I just had to die to
drag your attention from Stefan,
I would have tried it
a long time ago.
If you're trying to
make me feel guilty...
It's almost working.
I'm just glad you're here now.
Me, too.
I'm going to be a better
mother, starting right now.
I promise you... I'm
going to save your life.
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.MY-SUBS.Com/
she's brilliant.
We haven't noticed that
Katherine's been inhabiting.
Elena's body for weeks, and
that's all you have to say?
Yep.
And you realize that
it was Katherine who
broke up with you, it wasn't Elena.
Mm-hmm.
Right. So, your little murder spree
with Enzo where you killed Aaron,
you nearly killed Jeremy, tried
to kill Wes but you got infected
with that ripper virus...
That was all you
reacting to Katherine.
I'm trying to figure out why you
decided to tell a starving,
bloodthirsty, vampire-feeding
ripper that his Nemesis is still
walking around alive and well
while I am stuck in this cell
and can't do anything about it.
I have it under control.
I'd love to hear this.
Hang on here.
Katherine's still alive?
How is that even possible?
Remember that time Nadia's ex
Gregor hitched a ride in your head?
Ok, well, it's kind
of the same thing.
Katherine is a passenger in Elena,
except it's worse because
none of us seemed to notice.
She was at my house.
How did none of us figure it out?
Because it's Katherine,
and she's smart,
and conniving and sneaky
and...
We're the worst friends ever.
This makes no sense.
She saved my life.
She gave me CPR when
Enzo tried to kill me.
Katherine would never do that.
That's what made her so believable.
She played Elena to a t.
If she let you die,
her cover was blown.
I was sleeping
3 feet away from her.
She picked out
my bitter ball dress.
And I let her use my toothpaste.
Yeah, well, did she lure you into a
hotel room to make out with you?
She's the reason I found out
about you and Klaus.
Of course.
Oh, my God.
So, how do we kill the bitch?
Well, passengers can be
expelled from the host.
Saw it happen with Matt.
Gregor died and Matt lived.
All we have to do is
stab her with a traveler knife.
I still have the knife
that Nadia gave me.
Perfect. Go get it.
Hold on, guys, this is Katherine
that we're talking about.
She's gonna see a sneak attack
coming from a mile away.
We gotta get her to come to us.
Get her guard down.
Corner her.
Fat chance you'll be
seeing her today.
I'm pretty sure I bit Nadia.
What do you mean you bit her?
I mean she was attacking Caroline
and I might've nipped her a little.
And you're just
mentioning this now?
Hey, guys, focus.
Tyler's right.
Katherine is not
going to leave Nadia's side
unless not leaving
compromises her identity.
Which means?
We gotta invite her to something
that Elena can't say no to.
A surprise party?
Seriously?
I wanted a spa day.
You try feeling the death of every
supernatural creature
who passes through you
on their way to the other side.
I'm not saying
you don't deserve it.
Besides, your birthday
isn't until next week.
That's what makes it a surprise.
Yeah, I don't think Bonnie would
want a big party for her birthday.
Of course she does.
So, when can you get over to
Stefan's to help us set up?
I can't.
You can't.
I would love to,
but I just... I can't.
Um... I'm making arrangements
for Aaron Whitmore's funeral.
The only reason Damon killed him
was because we broke up, so,
I kind of feel like
I owe it to Aaron.
You understand, right?
Of course.
No, that's really nice of you.
Elena, you're so popular today.
Hey, Bonnie.
Hey. How's it going?
You sound tired.
Yeah. I had to pull an all-nighter
for my sociology exam
and then woke up to a coven of
dead Russian witches passing through
me on the way to the other side.
Sorry. Self-pity.
So not cute.
No, I totally get it.
You're the anchor now.
That must be...
exhausting.
Do you want to maybe meet up
for a coffee or something?
It's just been one of
those days, you know?
Yeah. Well, ha!
This is gonna sound crazy, but I'm
actually at the day spa right now
buying you a gift certificate
for your birthday.
It was supposed to be a surprise
but, well, surprise!
You read my mind.
That's so you.
Hey, look, I'll check
in with you later.
Ok.
Why are
they being so clingy today?
What are you doing?
There you go. Drink.
I need more.
Too bad.
That was nothing.
That's exactly 4 ounces.
When you were out killing vampires,
you said one vampire
kept you good for 8 hours.
So, our friend Caroline did a
little bit of math... Caroline?
Relax. She had a calculator.
So, 4 ounces 3 times a day
should be just enough
to help manage the hunger.
You mean manage me.
So you don't rip anyone's head off.
We'll deal with your crisis
once we get Elena back.
I'll deal with my own crisis.
Listen, you just
let me out of here.
I'll find Wes, I'll
get the antidote.
And then what, huh?
You skip town?
Leave it to me to tell Elena
everything you did after you thought
she broke up with you?
Who are you calling there, buddy?
Katherine's been making
a lot of excuses
and I have a feeling she won't
be able to say no to me.
It's your phone.
Elena is calling.
Answer it.
Elena. Hey.
Hey. Um... how are you?
Well, you know.
Strung up, hungry.
Same old, same old.
Now that the dust has settled, I was
hoping that, I don't know, maybe
we can talk about what
happened at the farmhouse.
Can I see you?
Ok. Sure.
Why don't you just come to the house
and we'll talk about it here?
Perfect.
I'll see you soon.
Ok. Bye.
Damon knows that he tried to
kill me less than 24 hours ago.
There isn't a single
vampire-craving bone in his body
that would risk putting
his precious Elena
back in that kind of danger again.
And yet he's desperate to see her.
Just like her other friends.
They know.
Doesn't make any sense.
She's dodged everyone's attempt
to try to get her over here.
Now she voluntarily
wants to come over?
Unless...
Unless?
She was testing me.
She knows.
Money for information.
I was told you saw Katerina
Petrova kill a man in cold blood
outside the court of versailles.
I want to know if that's true.
I want to know what kind
of person my mother is.
She's been on the run
for... 228 years.
You passed out in the car.
I didn't want to wake you.
Huh. Perfect.
I can make my peace
with the universe.
Don't talk like that. I brought
you here so that I could hide you
till Wes finds a way to heal you.
You should leave now.
While you can.
There's no point
in trying to save me.
I didn't raise you to be a quitter.
And I promise... As soon as you
get better, we're leaving.
Together.
Of course.
The farther she gets,
the worse our chances
are of ever seeing Elena again.
It's bad enough that we didn't
recognize Katherine.
We also just blew
our only advantage.
Nothing a little
locator spell can't fix.
Let me guess.
Matter of life and death?
Kind of. Yeah, um, do
you remember that locator spell
we did the other night?
Sure. We ended up saving him.
You're welcome, by the way.
Now we need you to find his sister.
Why? She run away from home?
No. She's been possessed
by her evil doppelganger.
Ok...
Liv.
Will you help us?
I can be convinced.
Need blood.
You just had your lunch
30 minutes ago.
Or you could give me a couple
sips of that hybrid juice.
I can be on my way and I'll take
up my ripper situation with Wes.
Not gonna happen.
Can I ask you a question without
you getting all wolf man on me?
Do I have a choice?
Why are you still here?
I'm a hybrid and you
need a baby-sitter.
Oh, no, I mean here here,
in Mystic Falls here.
Your famila's all dead
and I don't see you
getting a job at the Grill.
Yet I don't see you
in a Whitmore hoodie, either.
Something tells me
that there's a little
masochistic voice inside your head
that's trying to convince you
that you and Caroline still
have a fighting chance in hell.
I think you have enough problems
without having to worry about me.
You're probably right.
One small difference
between you and me...
- You want to hear it?
- Not especially.
You see, even after
all the terrible things I do,
Elena still chose me.
Because she's fighting for me.
Caroline, on the other hand,
chose the nuclear option.
You know that big,
red button that just
nukes your entire relationship
once and for all?
Well, sleeping with the
guy that killed your mom
was kind of her way of
slamming her hand down.
You think Elena will still
want you back after this?
It's over, Damon.
Fix yourself and run.
Far away.
I plan on it.
How's New Orleans
this time of year?
You really think
Elena's gonna forgive you?
Look at you.
You killed her friend.
You almost killed her brother.
You nearly killed her.
You're a joke, Damon.
Says the guy pining after
the girl who slept with Klaus.
You don't know anything about me.
I know how to get you in this cell.
Ooh! Aah!
Hey, ready for a changing of the guard...
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God. Tyler?
- I'm ok.
- He fed on you?
- I said I'm fine.
- Why would you come in here?
- Why do you think?
Damon knew exactly
how to piss me off.
What the hell happened?
I think Damon went to go find Wes.
Elena's necklace.
Candle. Map.
Give me your hand.
You're Elena's brother.
That makes you blood.
So, hand it over.
Actually, he's her cousin.
It's a long story.
Whatever.
Close enough.
That's not...
That's not how I taught you.
Relax, Mr. Miyagi.
I'm feeling my way through it, ok?
Now, what do I say, again?
Phesmatos tribum nas ex viras,
sequitas sanguinem.
Phesmatos tribum nas ex
viras, sequitas sanguinem.
Does Elena look anything like you?
Uh, same color hair.
What about her eyes?
Are they as pretty as yours?
Is this really necessary?
I'm sorry. I'm searching for his
sister/cousin's doppelganger
in my mind.
I'll take all the help I can get.
Phesmatos tribum nas ex viras,
sequitas sanguinem.
Phesmatos tribum nas ex
viras, sequitas... sanguinem.
Does your sister spend
a lot of time in church?
Are you leaving?
I'm going to check on Wes.
He's taking too long.
Be careful.
They're all out looking for you.
That's never stopped me before.
Huh.
Hello?
What's up, doc?
How did you find me?
I called my friend Enzo
and asked him about
the little adventure
he had with you.
Gotta say, long way off
the tenure track, huh?
Huh. I take it the Augustine society
hit a bit of a rough streak.
There is no Augustine
society, Damon.
It's just me.
Well, then I guess you're my guy.
You see, I have this
long road ahead of me
to win my ex-girlfriend back.
But I don't have a chance in hell
if I'm lusting over her blood.
Follow?
Even if I did cure you of this
virus, what difference does it make?
So you stop feeding on your friends
and go back to feeding
on innocent people.
Is that really gonna
impress Elena Gilbert?
Look at me.
You did this to me.
I didn't do this to you.
You are this.
I simply held up the mirror.
Now it's my turn to play doctor.
That was fun.
You think?
You must really trust Rebekah.
Huh?
Watch this.
I'm going to steal her earrings...
And you're not going
to say anything.
See? You're hanging out
with an original vampire
and you're not even
on vervain. Trust.
You know she's an original?
I recognized her
on the dance floor.
I was hoping she'd
know something about
her brother Klaus'
favorite vampire:
Katherine Pierce.
Maybe you heard of her?
Yeah. Yeah, I've heard of her.
I know her.
Why do you care?
Because she is my mother, and
I'd very much like to meet her.
I'm going to take your ring.
Now I have a reason
to see you again.
Wes? What the hell
is taking so I...
No. No.
Please, no. No.
Nadia, I'm coming back
to the church right now.
She's not at the church anymore.
She's with me at home.
Stefan, why do you have
Nadia's phone?
She doesn't have much
time left, Katherine.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I know that it's you and I
know that you care about Nadia.
That's why I brought her here.
Prove it.
Put her on the phone.
Katherine?
Run.
You can always run, Katherine.
It's what you do best.
Or you can come home
and see your daughter
one last time before she dies.
It's your choice.
Your hands are like ice.
Gregor.
No, it's Matt.
I'm not...
Gregor, I'm sorry I betrayed you.
I did it for my mother.
I did everything for her.
I know you did.
Forgive me?
Yes. I forgive you.
Hey, hey. Shh.
It's ok.
It's ok. Shh.
I... I don't want to die.
I don't want to die.
What's gonna happen when I die?
I'll take your hand...
And you'll go to the other side.
Just like that.
Will it hurt?
You won't feel any pain.
I'm here to see my daughter.
Nadia.
You came back for me.
I won't leave you again.
Did you find a way to save me?
Klaus' blood would've saved you...
If I'd asked for it.
You would have outed yourself.
But you would've been alive.
And now it's too late.
My mother's name is Katherine.
I'm looking for her.
You found me.
Nadia, I'm right here.
She's a liar.
And a murderer.
She manipulates.
She betrays.
She will do anything to survive.
Nadia. No, I'm...
I'm right here.
Nadia, look at me.
Look at me.
I'm here.
I'm right here.
I'm looking for my mother.
This is not what your
life should've been.
500 years searching for a mother
who ended up...  being me.
Let me show you what
your life should've been.
What your perfect day
would have been like.
You and I had a little cottage.
It was an ordinary summer day.
You'd been playing outside.
So, you were tired
and it was time for bed.
You told me about
the fort that you'd built.
Out in the woods by the river.
And so I asked if I could visit.
And you said when the sun came
up in the morning, and I said...
Good night, Nadia.
Sleep well.
Your mother loves you.
Uhh!
So.
This is it.
Hello, Katherine.
You didn't think I'd
miss this, did you?
Ok. So.
Who's got the knife?
Which one of you is gonna get to
kill the elusive Katherine Pierce
once and for all?
What? Suddenly
everyone's speechless?
When I was on my deathbed,
you all had plenty to say.
Is it you, Tyler?
Because I triggered
the werewolf curse?
Gave you an identity
and made you matter?
You've done nothing for me.
Oh, please, Tyler.
If I hadn't walked into your life,
you'd just be a wasted nobody
with a boozy mom
and a temper problem.
Don't. Don't.
And you.
I'm not worried
about you offing me.
Because we both know I made you
better by making you a vampire.
Good-bye, Katherine.
Bye-bye, Caroline.
Ooh. The one girl here
who actually appreciates
how beautiful you are.
You wouldn't stab me
in the heart, would you?
No, I don't think so.
You will definitely go down
as the best night I never had.
- Oh, well.
Well, little Gilbert, it
was nice to have a brother
for a second there.
When you weren't being
so damn annoying!
Bon Bon, no need for good-byes.
I'll see you on the flip side.
Damon. Oh, how you'd love nothing
more than to drive that blade
right through me.
We've already done this, Kitty Kat.
I've said all I needed to say.
I know, but I never got to say
what I needed to say to you.
I'm sorry.
You blame me for who you are.
And I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I turned you.
I'm sorry that you
didn't get to die
as a forgotten nobody
on a bloody battlefield,
and your father didn't
get to live another day
to be disgraced by you.
Damon, I'm sorry that I
gave your life purpose.
Passion. Drive. Desire.
I'm sorry that you are who you are
because I'm the one that
taught you how to love.
I'll see you in hell, Katherine.
Stefan.
You know, I always wondered what it
would be like to be loved by you.
You've got to admit, that
one fleeting moment...
Your feelings were real.
This truly has been
the role of a lifetime.
Stefan, I love you.
I've always loved you.
Mmf.
Uhh. I guess this is how...
Our love story ends.
Stefan said we should
bury her in the woods.
Screw that.
She deserves better.
You need some help?
No. I got this.
Why is she not waking up?
When Gregor left Matt's body, it
took him a while to wake up, too.
Which gives us a little bit of time
to talk about what
the hell you did.
Relax. Thanks to
Tyler's friendly donation,
I'll be fine for a couple hours.
A few hours, huh?
And then what?
What's the plan?
Tell her everything I did.
Let the chips crash
and burn where they may.
Optimistic.
I don't want to be
another Katherine Pierce.
Katherine spent her whole life
running from her problems
only to die here.
All alone.
- Is it wrong that I feel...
- Victorious?
Sad.
I know that Katherine is
a horrible person, but...
But you see the good in people.
You mean Klaus.
Because I saw the good in Klaus.
Your words.
Not mine.
Your hybrid bite just killed someone
and no one even batted an eye.
I sleep with the wrong guy weeks ago
and I don't hear the end of it.
- How is that fair?
- I don't know, Care.
Maybe people just
expect more from you.
Why? Because being good
comes so easy to me?
Well, guess what, Tyler?
It doesn't.
I am a vampire.
I have the same impulses as you.
So, I'm allowed to make
some mistakes along the way.
Yes, I slept with Klaus...
But after you walked away from me.
That was my choice
and I am living with it
and I don't need to be hearing
about it every 5 seconds.
So, just get over it or
get out of my life, but...
I'm done feeling guilty.
This is for you, dad.
I want you to know
how much I miss you.
You've got to be kidding me, right?
Something tells me I'm
about 5 centuries delayed
on the whole believing
in a higher power thing.
Well, you're here.
That means it worked.
You're dead.
True.
Then again, your friends
didn't really give me much of
a choice in the matter.
Using my only daughter against me?
Harsh.
I suppose I could've spent the next
500 years running, but for what?
My daughter was dying.
Stefan would never love me.
I was back to having nothing.
Elena wins again.
Let's get this over with.
I'm really starting
to get sick of Elena
getting everything that I want.
What is that supposed to mean?
Wes had no intention...
of helping Nadia.
You can always run, Katherine.
It's your choice.
Uhh!
A good day.
I've managed to extract
the werewolf venom
from Nadia Petrova's blood.
The addition of the venom
will make the ripper virus
even more lethal to vampires.
He was just using her
as a case study in his project
to wipe out vampires off
the face of the earth.
Why are you telling me this?
Hey. Elena?
I've said
it before and I'll say it again.
Elena had the life
I always wanted. Heh.
Well, until now.
Katherine, what did you do?
Stefan thought he gave me a choice:
Run or die.
But that's not really
much of a choice, is it?
After all, Nadia was
the only person
in this world who really loved me.
And I wasn't about to let
my daughter die alone.
But Katherine Pierce wasn't
about to go gentle, either.
Hi.
Are you... you?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's me.
I'm here.
I left
Elena with a little bit of
a parting gift.
If I can't have Stefan,
then no one can.
Ok. Now I'm ready.
Nothing's happening.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
This has never happened before.
Bonnie, what are you doing?
Let me pass through.
Why won't you let me pass through?
I don't know.
I don't control it.
- What?
- It's not up to me.
Then who is it up to?
- Bonnie.
- I can't help you, Katherine.
What... no, no no!
Nooooo!
Sync & corrections by Rafael UPD
www.MY-SUBS.com/